[
    {
        "type": "ORD",
        "question_text": "dispyt",
        "correct_answer": 2,
        "answers": ["brist", "gräl", "tvekan", "besvikelse", "undantag"],
        "additional_resorces": null
    },
    {
        "question_text": "angeläget",
        "answers": [
            "tydligt",
            "utmanande",
            "informativt",
            "noggrant",
            "viktigt"
        ],
        "type": "ORD",
        "correct_answer": 5,

        "additional_resorces": null
    },
    {
        "question_text": "supplement",
        "answers": ["verskott", "urval", "innehåll", "tillägg", "understöd"],
        "type": "ORD",
        "correct_answer": 4,
        "additional_resorces": null
    },
    {
        "question_text": "aktad",
        "answers": [
            "respekterad",
            "h\u00f6gtidlig",
            "artig",
            "f\u00f6rsiktig",
            "undanskymd"
        ],
        "type": "ORD",
        "additional_resorces": null
    },
    {
        "question_text": "rata",
        "answers": [
            "granska",
            "avvisa",
            "fastst\u00e4lla",
            "ifr\u00e5gas\u00e4tta",
            "samordna"
        ],
        "type": "ORD",
        "correct_answer": 2,
        "additional_resorces": null
    },
    {
        "question_text": "illa \u00e5tg\u00e5ngen",
        "answers": [
            "helt uttorkad",
            "n\u00e4stan slut",
            "mycket ledsen",
            "sv\u00e5rt angripen",
            "l\u00e4mnad utanf\u00f6r"
        ],
        "type": "ORD",
        "correct_answer": 4,
        "additional_resorces": null
    },
    {
        "question_text": "b\u00e4rkraft",
        "answers": [
            "avlagring",
            "prestation",
            "tryck",
            "h\u00e5llbarhet",
            "f\u00f6rs\u00f6rjning"
        ],
        "type": "ORD",
        "correct_answer": 4,
        "additional_resorces": null
    },
    {
        "question_text": "vegetera",
        "answers": [
            "tala g\u00e5tfullt",
            "vara gener\u00f6s",
            "leva i overksamhet",
            "besv\u00e4ra i on\u00f6dan",
            "sprida oro"
        ],
        "type": "ORD",
        "correct_answer": 3,
        "additional_resorces": null
    },
    {
        "type": "ORD",
        "question_text": "dispyt",
        "correct_answer": 2,
        "answers": ["brist", "gräl", "tvekan", "besvikelse", "undantag"]
    },
    {
        "type": "ORD",
        "question_text": "dispyt",
        "correct_answer": 2,
        "answers": ["brist", "gräl", "tvekan", "besvikelse", "undantag"]
    },
    {
        "type": "ORD",
        "question_text": "dispyt",
        "correct_answer": 2,
        "answers": ["brist", "gräl", "tvekan", "besvikelse", "undantag"]
    }
]
